let questions = [{
        "question": "Who invented HTML?",
        "answer_1": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "answer_2": "Tim Berners-Lee",
        "answer_3": "Lee Jones", // Lela Lee
        "answer_4": "Bruce Lee",
        "right_answer": 2,
    },
    // {
    //     "question": "What happens when JavaScript runs the alert() function?",
    //     "answer_1": "JavaScript checks to see if there are any unprocessed events",
    //     "answer_2": "A message is sent back to the PHP code to be logged on the server",
    //     "answer_3": "JavaScript pops up a dialog box and execution continues until the </alert> tag is encountered",
    //     "answer_4": "JavaScript execution is paused and a dialog box pops up",
    //     "right_answer": 4,
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "Which of the following is not a way to include JavaScript in an HTML document?",
    //     "answer_1": "By including the code in the < ? javascript and ? \ >tags", //wie html code escapen?
    //     "answer_2": "By including the code between < script > and < / script > tags",
    //     "answer_3": "By including a file containing JavaScript using a tag",
    //     "answer_4": "On a tag using an attribute like onclick=”” ",
    //     "right_answer": 1,
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What happens in a normal end-user’s browser when there is a JavaScript error?",
    //     "answer_1": "JavaScript logs the error to the PHP error log",
    //     "answer_2": "JavaScript prints a traceback indicating the line in error",
    //     "answer_3": "JavaScript skips the line in error and continues executing after the next semicolon (;)",
    //     "answer_4": "Nothing except perhaps a small red error icon that is barely noticeable",
    //     "right_answer": 4,
    // },
    {
        "question": "Where can a developer find which line in a web page of JavaScript file is causing a syntax error?",
        "answer_1": "By looking at a file on the hard disk of the system where the browser is running",
        "answer_2": "In the developer console in the browser",
        "answer_3": "Do a “View Source” to see the HTML source code",
        "answer_4": "In the PHP error log",
        "right_answer": 2,
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is <strong>not</strong> a valid JavaScript variable name?",
        "answer_1": "3peat",
        "answer_2": "$_data",
        "answer_3": "$_DATA",
        "answer_4": "_data",
        "right_answer": 4,
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between strings with single quotes and double quotes in JavaScript?",
        "answer_1": "Double quoted strings so variable substitution for variables that start with dollar sign ($)",
        "answer_2": "There is no difference",
        "answer_3": "Single quoted strings do not treat \n as a newline",
        "answer_4": "Double quotes strings cannot be used in JavaScript",
        "right_answer": 2,
    },
    // {
    //     "question": "What is the meaning of the “triple equals” operator (===) in JavaScript?",
    //     "answer_1": "",
    //     "answer_2": "",
    //     "answer_3": "Both sides of the triple equals operator are converted to boolean before comparison",
    //     "answer_4": "That the values being compared are the same without any type conversion",
    //     "right_answer": 4,
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "How do you indicate that a variable reference within a JavaScript function is a global (i.e. not local) variable?",
    //     "answer_1": "Use the keyword “global” to declare the variable in the function",
    //     "answer_2": "Use the keyword “var” to declare the variable in the function",
    //     "answer_3": "Nothing, simply declare the variable globally before the function definition in the code",
    //     "answer_4": "Use the keyword “global” when declaring the variable outside the function",
    //     "right_answer": 3,
    // },
    {
        "question": "How many programmers do you need to change a lightbulb?",
        "answer_1": "2",
        "answer_2": "202",
        "answer_3": "3.33",
        "answer_4": "NULL (This is a hardware problem).",
        "right_answer": 4,
    }
];